Division of Invertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Labels, 1864-Present; Series II
  - Slide Box Labels. Archived labels from the Microslide IMLS project., 1864-Present; 000983
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Loligo Gonatus, 1864-Present; 000451
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. OLIGOCHEATA Misc, 1864-Present; 000452
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. OLIGOCHEATA Haplotaxidae etc., 1864-Present; 000453
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. OLIGOCHEATA Lumbricus terrestris, 1864-Present; 000454
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. THAILAND IV YPM Nos. 8344 - 8358, 1864-Present; 000455
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. THAILAND III YPM Nos. 8245-8261, 8313-8342, 1864-Present; 000456
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. THAILAND II YPM Nos. 8198 - 8244B, 1864-Present; 000457
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. THAILAND I YPM Nos. 8150 - 8197, 1864-Present; 000458
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. THAILAND I YPM Nos. 8150 - 8197, 1864-Present; 000459
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Infernalis Epithelium Conn. Tissue Misc(e)llany, 1864-Present; 000460
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. V. Infernalis Heart Skin, 1864-Present; 000461
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Vampyroteuthis Brain Filament Stellate Gangl Olf. Organ Light Organs, 1864-Present; 000462
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Vampyroteuthis (sections) Eye, 1864-Present; 000463
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PORIFERA - TYPE MATERIAL Demospongiae other than Dictyoceratida, 1864-Present; 000464
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box., 1864-Present; 000465
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. JAMAICA - NORTH COAST YPM Nos. 4614 - 5331, 1864-Present; 000466
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Unstained Sections, 1864-Present; 000467
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. UNSTAINED SECTIONS Calcarea, 1864-Present; 000468
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. UNSTAINED SECTIONS - DICTYOCERATIDA, 1864-Present; 000469
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. UNSTAINED SECTIONS - Ifaluk - II, 1864-Present; 000470
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. UNSTAINED SECTIONS - Ifaluk - I, 1864-Present; 000471
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Paranemertes pallida YPM Nos. 118, 120, 121, 1864-Present; 000472
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Paranemertes peregrina YPM Nos. 122, 123, 124., 1864-Present; 000473
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Paranemertes californica Coe YPM Nos. 125, 126, 127, 128, 1864-Present; 000474
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Paranemertes californica Coe YPM Nos. 129, 130, 131, 132., 1864-Present; 000475
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Scripps Si 32, 1864-Present; 000476
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Suberites undulatus, 1864-Present; 000477
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Isodictya, 1864-Present; 000478
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Temperature H. loosanoffi, 1864-Present; 000479
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Bermuda Coll. Provenzano, 1864-Present; 000480
    - Slide Box Labels. small black slide box with no External or internal labels, 1864-Present; 000481
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Cuba W. L. Schmidtt, 1864-Present; 000482
    - Slide Box Labels. internal label of slide box., 1864-Present; 000483
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Bryozoa, 1864-Present; 000484
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Tethya Misc-Little, 1864-Present; 000485
    - Slide Box Labels. small black slide box with no External or internal labels, 1864-Present; 000486
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Cliona-Cape May GBD, 1864-Present; 000487
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Lamont, 1864-Present; 000488
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Suberites Mediterranean, 1864-Present; 000489
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Vera Cruz Texas Hildebrand, 1864-Present; 000490
    - Slide Box Labels. small black slide box with no External or internal labels, 1864-Present; 000491
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Paranemertes californica Coe YPM Nos. 133, 134, 1864-Present; 000492
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Bahamas -- P E Cloud, 1864-Present; 000493
    - Slide Box Labels. small black slide box with no External or internal labels, 1864-Present; 000494
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Stelletta, Geodia, 1864-Present; 000495
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Spongia, 1864-Present; 000496
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Halichondria bowerbanki Europe and USA, 1864-Present; 000497
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Microciona prolifera, 1864-Present; 000498
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. H. rayae, 1864-Present; 000499
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. DIATOMES CXXXVII, 1864-Present; 000500
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Hymenoptera, 1864-Present; 000501
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. ASTERIAS STRONGYLOCENTROTUS CXXIX, 1864-Present; 000502
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Oligochaetes - Leeches Dem. Material, 1864-Present; 000503
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. PLANTS 2, 1864-Present; 000504
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. PLANTS 3, 1864-Present; 000505
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. HEXAPODA Embryology Aphids, 1864-Present; 000506
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. CXXXI ECHINODERMATA HOLOTHUROIDEA, 1864-Present; 000507
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. ECHINODERMATA HOLOTHUROIDEA 2, 1864-Present; 000508
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. ECHINODERMATA ECHINOIDEA 1, 1864-Present; 000509
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. PLANTS CXXXIX, 1864-Present; 000510
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. TEST PLATES 1, 1864-Present; 000511
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. HEXAPODA Nervous System, 1864-Present; 000512
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. CELITE TEST PLATES 2, 1864-Present; 000513
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Gyropidae, 1864-Present; 000514
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. BUGS, 1864-Present; 000515
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. OPHIUROIDEA, 1864-Present; 000516
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. GLOSSINA PALP, 1864-Present; 000517
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. OPHIUROIDEA, 1864-Present; 000518
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. HEXAPODA Anopholes Culex, 1864-Present; 000519
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. INSECTS LARVAE XCV, 1864-Present; 000520
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. MALLOPHAGA (LIPEURUS), 1864-Present; 000521
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. MALLOPHAGA, 1864-Present; 000522
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. GASTROPODA RADULA, 1864-Present; 000523
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. MOLLUSCA BIVALVES + CEPHALOPODS DEM, 1864-Present; 000524
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. FLEAS, 1864-Present; 000525
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. FLEAS, 1864-Present; 000526
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. LICE, 1864-Present; 000527
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. MOLLUSCA GASTROPODA 1, 1864-Present; 000528
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. HEXAPODA Internal anatomy, 1864-Present; 000529
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. G. E. PICKFORD, 1864-Present; 000530
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. G. E. PICKFORD, 1864-Present; 000531
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. G. E. PICKFORD, 1864-Present; 000532
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. DIPTERA, 1864-Present; 000533
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Insect Wings XCVII, 1864-Present; 000534
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. HEXAPODA External anatomy 1, 1864-Present; 000536
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. CLADOCERA LVI, 1864-Present; 000537
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. LOLIGO Sections R.S. Lull, 1864-Present; 000538
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O. virginica O4. K-L. 05. A-I 06. A-E, 1864-Present; 000539
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O. virginica O, A-R, 1864-Present; 000540
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Modiolus Mod 32-59, 1864-Present; 000541
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Modiolus Mod 60B6 - 60D ser. secs. - 63, 1864-Present; 000542
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000543
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Ostrea lurida La Jolla Nos. 2, 1864-Present; 000544
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O3612 A-F O3613 A-K, 1864-Present; 000545
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O3615 A-Y, 1864-Present; 000546
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Mammary Gland, 1864-Present; 000547
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Spermatogenesis Ostrea virginica, 1864-Present; 000548
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Spermatogenesis Ostrea virginica, 1864-Present; 000549
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O. lurida 54-58H, 1864-Present; 000550
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Lamprey Eel Notochord, 1864-Present; 000551
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. 301673 Paradrionemertes 30652 Clumiella? 30276B 41-49, 1864-Present; 000552
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Nectonemertes mirabilis, 1864-Present; 000553
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. 30276B Nectonemertes mirabilis, 1864-Present; 000554
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Beebe Nemertes, 1864-Present; 000555
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. EURYPANOPEUS depressus, 1864-Present; 000556
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. BACTERIA, 1864-Present; 000557
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. PHERETIMA, 1864-Present; 000558
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. EURYPANOPEUS depressus, 1864-Present; 000559
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Dolichopteryx Aceratias, 1864-Present; 000560
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: OLIGOCHAETA 7 (Pheretima), 1864-Present; 000561
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: OLIGOCHAETA 6 (Pheretima), 1864-Present; 000562
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: Lamellibranchia, 1864-Present; 000563
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000564
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000565
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: Regeneration Lineus socialis 54D T P F A B, 1864-Present; 000566
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: Carinella rubra Virgin Bay, 1864-Present; 000567
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: Mya M3786 - M3798 Serial sections, 1864-Present; 000568
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: Rotifers, 1864-Present; 000569
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: Box 2 Testudinellidae 1-17 Flosculariidae 18-47 Gastropodidae 48-50 Notommatidae 51-84 Collothecidae 85-100, 1864-Present; 000570
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: Box 3 Lecanidae 1-57, 100 Trichocercidae 58-99, 1864-Present; 000571
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: Box 4 Birgeidae 47 Brachionidae 48-54 Flosculariidae Collothecidae 85-100, 1864-Present; 000572
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: BARBADOS PORIFERA J.B. Lewis Coll., 1864-Present; 000573
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: BARBADOS PORIFERA - II J.B. Lewis Coll., 1864-Present; 000574
    - Slide Box Labels. External and Internal label of slide box: JAMAICA - PORT ROYAL, 1864-Present; 000575
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: ZOOPLANKTON, 1864-Present; 000576
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: slides belong to WDH, 1864-Present; 000577
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000578
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Regeneration Lineus socialis, 1864-Present; 000579
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Cephalothrix spiralis Male, 1864-Present; 000580
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Crepidula convexa, 1864-Present; 000581
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Anomia A21F-A21M, 1864-Present; 000582
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: 51A 7 days 51A-F days, 1864-Present; 000583
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Modiolus 93C-97, 1864-Present; 000584
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000585
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Modiolus 201 A-207 Mod. 1-14, 1864-Present; 000586
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: O. virginica O6-F-S, 1864-Present; 000587
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: 57 Cephalothrix spiralis male, 1864-Present; 000588
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Modioluus Mod 60 A-B5 Serial Sections, 1864-Present; 000589
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Modiolus modiolus 67-93B, 1864-Present; 000590
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Cephalothrix spiralis, 1864-Present; 000591
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000592
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: O3639A-O3642N, 1864-Present; 000593
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Anomia A1-21E, 1864-Present; 000594
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Teredo 101 Q-BB 102 A-M 103 A-F, 1864-Present; 000595
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000596
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: 57 Cephalothrix spiralis Female, 1864-Present; 000597
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Teredo 122, 1864-Present; 000598
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Tridacna Mantle Edge, 1864-Present; 000599
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: DENDRONOTUS, 1864-Present; 000600
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Mytilus Mantle Gills, 1864-Present; 000601
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Eyes Pecten maximus T.S. & L.S., 1864-Present; 000602
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: GASTROPODA DEM, 1864-Present; 000603
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: MOLLUSCA CEPHALOPODA 2, 1864-Present; 000604
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: LOLIGO XLVIII, 1864-Present; 000605
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: SQUID LARVA, 1864-Present; 000606
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000607
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: HEXAPODA Protura Thysanura, 1864-Present; 000608
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: HEXAPODA Periplaneta 1, 1864-Present; 000609
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. HEXAPODA Periplaneta 2, 1864-Present; 000610
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000611
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. HEXAPODA Lepisma, 1864-Present; 000612
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Insects External anatomy XCVI, 1864-Present; 000613
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Insects-sections Head LXX, 1864-Present; 000614
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Mya C24-50, 1864-Present; 000615
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Periplanata, 1864-Present; 000616
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Mya 37114-37125, 1864-Present; 000617
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. LICE, 1864-Present; 000618
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. COCKROACH sections, 1864-Present; 000619
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Mya 37109, 1864-Present; 000620
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Periplaneta americana Head, 1864-Present; 000621
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Crepidula F359-3512 F361; F369 Teredo 346-348, 1864-Present; 000622
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Crepidula plana P21-, 1864-Present; 000623
    - Slide Box Labels. Notes from slide boxl. Polychaete setae slides, 1864-Present; 000624
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe, 1864-Present; 000625
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe, 1864-Present; 000626
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe imbricata, 1864-Present; 000627
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe, 1864-Present; 000628
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box: Lagisca impatiens, 1864-Present; 000629
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe (Lagisca), 1864-Present; 000630
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe (Lagisca), 1864-Present; 000631
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe (Lagisca) (Evarne), 1864-Present; 000632
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe (Eunoa)(Lagisca), 1864-Present; 000633
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Harmothoe (Eunoa), 1864-Present; 000634
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Nychia, 1864-Present; 000635
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Lepidonotus, 1864-Present; 000636
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Polynoe + others, 1864-Present; 000637
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Sigalion Sthenelais, 1864-Present; 000638
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Euphrosyne Spinther, 1864-Present; 000639
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Aphrodite Laetmatonice, 1864-Present; 000640
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Nephthys Nereis, 1864-Present; 000641
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Nothria Leodice Nereis sp. nov., 1864-Present; 000642
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Nereis Diopatra Leodice, 1864-Present; 000643
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels for big box containing 19 slide boxes. Annelida Bush, 1864-Present; 000644
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Kirkpatrickia, 1864-Present; 000645
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Kirkpatrickia, 1864-Present; 000646
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Mya serial sections, 1864-Present; 000647
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Cephalothrix spinalis Male, 1864-Present; 000648
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Barnea B1-7 Teredo T361A-M, 1864-Present; 000649
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. 30276 Nectonemertes mirabilis, 1864-Present; 000650
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. 57 Cephalothrix spiralis, 1864-Present; 000651
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Teredo 341-345, 1864-Present; 000652
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Crepidula formicata FXE-FX1A, 1864-Present; 000653
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Cerebratulus lacteus, 1864-Present; 000654
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Cephalothrix, 1864-Present; 000655
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Nectonemertes mirabilis, 1864-Present; 000656
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Cephalothrix spiralis Coe June 1929 Woods Hole, 1864-Present; 000657
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. O. virginica, 1864-Present; 000658
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. 210= M. Caeca V. 236= C. Lacteus C. Leidyi, 1864-Present; 000659
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Cephalothrix spiralis, 1864-Present; 000660
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. CARINELLA pellucida Coe, 1864-Present; 000661
    - Slide Box Labels. External abels of slide box. Cephalothrix spiralis Coe Woods Hole June 1929, 1864-Present; 000662
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ketchikan, Alaska September, 2003, 1864-Present; 000663
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Diatomes CXXVII, 1864-Present; 000664
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Mya 3712OC, 1864-Present; 000665
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Mya-- My1-25 with shells Sept 1927, 1864-Present; 000666
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Mya m3777-m3794, 1864-Present; 000667
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Ostrea lurida 1400-1404, 1864-Present; 000668
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Lineus arenicola Verr St. Andrews, P.E.I. Slides 1-16, 1864-Present; 000669
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Crustacea, 1864-Present; 000670
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Ketchikan, Alaska, 1864-Present; 000671
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Ketchikan, Alaska, 1864-Present; 000672
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Island of Hawaii USA, 1864-Present; 000673
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Island of Hawaii USA, 1864-Present; 000674
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Ketchikan, AK, 1864-Present; 000675
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Ketchikan, Alaska, 1864-Present; 000676
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Poeobius, 1864-Present; 000677
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box. Poeobius meseres, 1864-Present; 000678
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box. Poeobius, 1864-Present; 000679
    - Slide Box Labels. Index card label of slide box. Poeobius, 1864-Present; 000680
    - Slide Box Labels. Index card label of slide box. Poeobius, 1864-Present; 000681
    - Slide Box Labels. Index card label of slide box. Poeobius, 1864-Present; 000682
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels for slide box., 1864-Present; 000686
    - Slide Box Labels. Original label for slide box. Evacis rosea + rubra rugosa robusta, nivea, socilaria citrina petrosa, 1864-Present; 000687
    - Slide Box Labels. External label for slide box 5797 (part), 1864-Present; 000688
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels for slide box 8100 + 8139, 1864-Present; 000689
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels for slide box 6533 - 6568, 1864-Present; 000690